In the coming era of budget cuts to education, distance learning could become the norm.
削减教育预算的时代即将到来，届时远程学习可能会成为常态。
The temptation for those in charge of education budgets to trade teachers for technology could be so strong that they ignore the disadvantages of distance learning.
对主管教育预算的人来说，把教师换成技术的诱惑可能强烈到让他们忽视远程学习的弊端。
School facilities are expensive to build and maintain, and teachers are expensive to employ.
学校设施的建造和维护费用高昂，聘用教师的开支也很大。
Online classes do not require buildings, and each class can host hundreds of people simultaneously, resulting in greater savings, thus increasing the temptation of distance education for those concerned more about budgets than learning.
网课不需要校舍，而且每堂课都能同时容纳数百人，因而能省下更多开支，这就让远程教育对那些更关心预算而不是学习的人更具诱惑力。
But moving away from a traditional classroom in which a living, breathing human being teaches and interacts with students daily would be a disaster.
但在传统课堂上，一个活生生的人每天给学生上课、与他们互动，告别这样的课堂将会是一场灾难。
Physically attending school has hidden benefits: getting up every morning, interacting with peers, and building relationships with teachers are essential skills to cultivate in young people.
亲身到校上学有隐性的好处：每天早起、与同龄人互动、与老师建立关系，都是需要在年轻人身上培养的必备技能。
Moreover, schools should be more than simple institutions of traditional learning.
此外，学校应当不只是单纯的传统学习机构。
They are now places that provide meals.
如今，学校还是提供餐食的地方。
They are places where students receive counseling and other support.
学校也是学生接受辅导和其他支持的地方。
Those policy-makers are often fascinated by the latest technology in education and its potential to “transform” education overnight.
那些政策制定者常常迷恋教育领域的最新技术，迷恋它能在一夜之间“变革”教育的潜力。
But online education does not allow a teacher to keep a struggling student after class and offer help.
但网络教育无法让老师在课后留下学习吃力的学生，为他们提供帮助。
Educational videos may deliver academic content, but they are unable to make eye contact or assess a student’s level of engagement.
教学视频或许能传授学业内容，却无法和学生眼神交流，也无法评估学生的投入程度。
Distance education will never match the personal teaching in a traditional classroom.
远程教育永远比不上传统课堂中的面对面教学。
In their first 18 years of life, American children spend only 9% of their time in school.
在人生的头18年里，美国孩子只有9%的时间在学校度过。
Yet teachers are expected to prepare them to be responsible citizens, cultivate their social skills, encourage successful time management, and enhance their capacity to flourish in an increasingly harsh labor market.
然而，人们却期望老师让孩子们做好成为负责任公民的准备，培养他们的社交技能，鼓励他们管理好时间，并增强他们在日益严酷的劳动力市场中大展身手的能力。
Given these expectations, schools should not become permanently “remote”.
考虑到这些期望，学校不应该永久“远程化”。
The power of the classroom is rooted in the humanity of the people gathered in the same place, at the same time.
课堂的力量根植于同一时间、同一地点相聚的人们身上的人性。
Personal teaching is about teachers showing students a higher path, and about young people going through the process together.
面对面教学的要义，在于老师为学生指明一条更高远的道路，也在于年轻人一起经历这个过程。
Technology, no matter how advanced, should simply be a tool of a good teacher.
技术无论多么先进，都只应该是好老师的工具。